<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <style name="country_details_heading">
        <item name="android:layout_width">match_parent</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">wrap_content</item>
        <item name="android:color">#212121</item>
        <item name="android:textSize">24sp</item>
        <item name="android:paddingLeft">10sp</item>
        <item name="android:paddingRight">10sp</item>
        <item name="android:paddingTop">20sp</item>
    </style>

    <style name="country_details_value" parent="country_details_heading">
        <item name="android:textSize">34sp</item>
        <item name="android:paddingTop">10sp</item>
    </style>

    <style name="country_details_tour_desc">
        <item name="android:ellipsize">end</item>
        <item name="android:padding">5sp</item>
        <item name="android:lines">8</item>
        <item name="android:layout_weight">2</item>
        <item name="android:layout_width">0dp</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">match_parent</item>
    </style>

    <style name="country_details_tour_image">
        <item name="android:layout_weight">2</item>
        <item name="android:layout_width">0dp</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">match_parent</item>
        <item name="android:scaleType">centerCrop</item>
    </style>


    <string name="france_name">France</string>
    <string name="france_t1_description">The Eiffel Tower is the symbol of Paris and one of the top tourist attractions in France. The tower was built by Gustave Eiffel as the entrance arch for the International Exhibition of Paris of 1889. At 324 meters (1,063 feet) tall, it is still the highest building in Paris, offering stunning vistas of the city below. Since its construction more than 200,000,000 people have visited the Eiffel Tower making it the most visited paid tourist attraction in the world.</string>
    <string name="france_t2_description">St Tropez is a resort community on the French Riviera. Once a military stronghold, fishing village and artist colony, it is now a playground for the jetset, fashion models, and millionaires. The beaches are popular with scantily clad sunbathers, while others come for windsurfing, sailing, motorized water sports and yachting. Outside peak summer there are less celebrities to spot but you’ll also instantly appreciate what lured artists, writers and film makers to this picturesque village.</string>
    <string name="france_t3_description">Chamonix Valley is one of the oldest ski resorts in France. The first Winter Olympics was held here in 1924. It is located near Mont Blanc in the French Alps. In winter world-class skiers and boarders push themselves to extremes on Europe’s most challenging slopes while in the summer months Chamonix is a mecca for alpine mountaineers and mountain bikers. Riding a cable car through the mountains is popular in the summer as well.</string>
    <string name="france_t4_description">The Palace of Versailles is frequently associated with Marie Antoinette, the French queen who was beheaded during the French Revolution. The royal palace started out as a hunting lodge in 1624 and became more ornate over the years. Located outside of Paris, Versailles is known for the Hall of Mirrors and beautiful gardens.</string>
    <string name="france_t5_description">Mont Saint Michel is a small tidal island located just off the coast of Normandy. A spectacular and well-preserved Norman Benedictine Abbey of St Michel stands at the peak of the rocky island, surrounded by the winding streets and convoluted architecture of the medieval town. A causeway connects the mainland with the island.</string>

    <string name="germany_name">Germany</string>
    <string name="germany_t1_description">The ultimate fairytale castle, Neuschwanstein is situated on a rugged hill near Füssen in southwest Bavaria. It was the inspiration for the Sleeping Beauty castles in the Disneyland parks. The castle was commissioned by King Ludwig II of Bavaria who was declared insane when the castle was almost completed in 1886 and found dead a few days later. Neuschwanstein is the most photographed building in the country and one of the most popular tourist attractions in Germany.</string>
    <string name="germany_t2_description">The Brandenburg Gate is the only surviving city gate of Berlin and symbolizes the reunification of East and West Berlin. Built in the 18th century, the Brandenburg Gate is the entry to Unter den Linden, the prominent boulevard of linden trees which once led directly to the palace of the Prussian monarchs. It is regarded as one of the most famous landmarks in Europe.</string>
    <string name="germany_t3_description">Located in the Neckar river valley, Heidelberg is one Germany’s most popular tourist destinations. During WWII, the city was almost completely spared by allied bombings which destroyed most of Germany’s larger inner cities. As a result, Heidelberg has retained its baroque charm of narrow streets, picturesque houses and the famous Heidelberg Castle.</string>
    <string name="germany_t4_description">The Holstentor is one of the two remaining city gates of the city of Lübeck. Built in 1464, the gate now serves as a museum. Because of its two captivating round towers and arched entrance it is regarded as a symbol of Lübeck. Together with the old city center (Altstadt) of Lübeck it is one of the top tourist attractions in Germany.</string>
    <string name="germany_t5_description">Easily the greatest Gothic cathedral in Germany, Cologne Cathedral (Kölner Dom) has been Cologne’s most famous landmark for centuries. Construction of the Cologne Cathedral began in 1248 and took, with interruptions, more than 600 years to complete. It is dedicated to the saints Peter and Mary and is the seat of the Catholic Archbishop of Cologne.</string>

    <string name="belgium_name">Belgium</string>
    <string name="belgium_t1_description">Because of its canals Bruges is often called ‘The Venice of the North’. In the Middle Ages the ‘Reie’ river had been turned into a network of canals that enabled the traders to bring their products to the large Water Halls at the Market. Nowadays a boat ride on these famous canals provide a great way to see some of Bruges most beautiful sites.</string>
    <string name="belgium_t2_description">The Grand Place (or Grote Markt) is a must-see for visitors to Brussels. Indeed, this central square is the city’s main landmark. Surrounded by the town hall and guildhalls, the square isn’t very big, as squares around the world go but the old buildings that line its sides make it very special. The Grand Place dates back to the 11th century when markets were held. Nowadays, every two years in August, an enormous “flower carpet” is set up in the Grand Place for a few days. A million colorful begonias are set up in patterns covering a large part of the square.</string>
    <string name="belgium_t3_description">Visitors need to be in good physical shape if they want to climb the Belfry of Bruges as it is 366 steep, narrow steps to the top. Those who complete the climb of this important symbol of Bruges will be rewarded with great views of the city. The medieval bell tower dates back to 1240, built at a time when Bruges was a major player in the cloth industry. It was rebuilt after being destroyed by fire 40 years later, with other fires occurring in the centuries following. Bells still chime out from the tower today.</string>
    <string name="belgium_t4_description">Looking at the 12th century Gravensteen Castle, one can almost picture knights in shining armor riding white horses out the gates. Which wouldn’t be too far off, as the castle was patterned after the ones that the knights saw on the Second Crusade in the Middle Ages. Over the centuries it was used as a prison and factory, with houses built in the courtyard. Scheduled to be demolished, the city of Ghent rescued it in 1885 and renovated it. It is now one of the most popular tourist attractions in Belgium. Inside is a museum of torture devices used in Ghent over the ages.</string>
    <string name="belgium_t5_description">Catholicism has been an important religion in the Walloon city of Tournai since the 6th century, though construction of the Cathedral of Our Lady(Notre-Dame de Tournai) did not start until the 12th century. It features three architectural styles: Romanesque, Transitional and Gothic. The cathedral has five bell towers with ceilings that reach up to 157 feet high. The house of worship is also home to The Issue of Souls in Purgatory, a painting by the great Flemish artist, Peter Paul Rubens. The cathedral is undergoing renovation after it suffered major damage in a 1999 tornado.</string>


    <string name="italy_name">Italy</string>
    <string name="italy_t1_description">Formerly the capital of the Roman Empire, Rome today is the government seat and capital city of Italy. Located in the country’s central region of Lazio, Rome is a vast and complex city that is both historic and modern at the same time. Best known for housing ancient Roman structures and the Vatican City, Rome has endured for more than 2,500 years as an important center for culture, power and religion. From ancient romantic plazas to stunning cathedrals and Renaissance architecture, there is so much to see and do in Rome, that it could take months or even years to see it all.</string>
    <string name="italy_t2_description">Italy’s most famous region, Tuscany conjures images of beautiful rolling hills, olive groves, vineyards and cypress trees. The many pleasures of Tuscany include tasting wine in Chianti, simply relaxing in hill towns such as San Gimignano or exploring Renaissance art in Florence. The medieval city of Siena also holds excellent works of art while its historic center is one of the most popular places to visit in Italy. Elba, the largest of several Tuscan islands, offers great beaches while Pisa is world-famous for its Leaning Tower.</string>
    <string name="italy_t3_description">One of the best places to visit in Italy, Venice is a unique city in that is built upon a lagoon surrounded by the Adriatic Sea. Located in northeastern Italy, Venice is an archipelago of 118 islands all connected by hundreds of beautiful bridges and scenic canals. Of the canals, the Grand Canal is most famous and divides the city into two sections. Picturesque waterways and historic architecture make Venice one of the most romantic cities in the world. Venice is often crowded but well worth visiting to see its magnificent landmarks like Saint Mark’s Square and Basilica, Doge’s Palace and Rialto Bridge. One of the most popular things to do is to take a gondola ride along one of its many canals.</string>
    <string name="italy_t4_description">One of Italy’s most visited tourist destinations, Pompeii is a famous Roman city which was buried under several feet of volcanic ash for nearly 1,700 years after the cataclysmic eruption of Mt. Vesuvius. Excavation of Pompeii began in 1748, and the site is yet to be totally unearthed. The site is located near the modern city of Naples. A tour of Pompeii offers a fascinating insight into the everyday life of the ancient Roman world. Visitors can walk along the ancient streets to see the remains of bakeries, brothels and baths.</string>
    <string name="italy_t5_description">Situated in Italy’s southwestern region of Campania, the Amalfi Coast is known for its extraordinary beauty that makes it one of Italy’s top tourist destinations. Stretching 30 miles along the southern side of the Sorrento Peninsula, the Amalfi Coast is prized for its picturesque coastline that features shimmering bays, craggy cliffs, lemon tree gardens, multicolored villas and ritzy resorts. One of the most romantic and posh towns along the Amalfi Coast is Positano with its beautiful pebbled beaches, pastel houses and scenic mountains. One of the larger towns, Amalfi, features lovely plazas lined with restaurants while the town of Ravello is favored for its beautiful villas of gardens and art works.</string>

    <string name="spain_name">Spain</string>
    <string name="spain_t1_description">Located in northeastern Spain, Barcelona is one of the country’s top travel destinations because it offers everything tourists look for in a European city from historic architecture to lively shopping, vibrant culture and buzzing nightlife. Unique to Barcelona are the architectural marvels of Spain’s famous architect, Antoni Gaudi, which include the Casa Batllo and the famous Sagrada Familia church. Both of these extraordinary structures feature combinations of fascinating designs, shapes and colors. Popular activities in Barcelona include strolling along La Rambla, a tree-lined pedestrian avenue, and sunbath on Barceloneta, one of the city’s most popular beaches.</string>
    <string name="spain_t2_description">Located at the base of the Sierra Nevada mountains of southern Spain, Granada is the capital of the Granada province. Granada offers a perfect blend of traditional cultures, an animated nightlife and spectacular attractions including the world famous Alhambra, a pinnacle of Moorish art that encapsulates Andalusian history. This medieval complex overlooking Granada is one of the great architectural sights of Europe, with many visitors coming to Granada expressly to see the Alhambra. The last Moorish stronghold in Europe, the Alhambra offers the visitor splendid ornamental architecture, spectacular and lush gardens, cascading and dripping water features, and breathtaking views of the city below.</string>
    <string name="spain_t3_description">Spain has some of the most beautiful islands in Europe. The largest Spanish Islands are equally divided between the Balearic Islands and the Canary Islands. East of the Spanish mainland, the four chief Balearic Islands (Ibiza, Formentera, Mallorca and Menorca) maintain a character distinct from the rest of Spain and from each other. Mallorca is the largest and best-known Balearic island while Ibiza is famous as a party destination. The Canary Islands, also known as the Canaries, are located just off the southern coast of Morocco in the Atlantic. They are popular for their beautiful beaches, mild climate and important natural attractions, especially the Maspalomas Dunes in Gran Canaria and the Teide Volcano in Tenerife.</string>
    <string name="spain_t4_description">Spain’s capital and largest city, Madrid, is widely known for its sizzling nightlife scene. The city constitutes a diversity of ethnic groups, making it one of Europe’s most colorful cosmopolitan cities. Located within the city center are most of Madrid’s most popular tourist attractions such as the Royal Palace, the residence of Spain’s monarch. The heart of Madrid (and Spain) is Puerta del Sol, a large plaza serving as the scene of festivals, important gatherings and street performers as well as a hub for the public transportation network. Another important square is Plaza Mayor, known for the lively San Miguel Market.</string>
    <string name="spain_t5_description">Exceptional tourist attractions, lively festivals and buzzing nightlife all make Seville one of the best places to visit in Spain. As the capital city of Andalusia, Seville is also the region’s financial and cultural capital. The city is home to many beautiful and important historic landmarks, chief of which is the grand Cathedral of Seville, where it is believed that Christopher Columbus is buried. Another significant building is the Real Alcazar, an extravagant Moorish palace with luxurious gardens.</string>

</resources>